易考范文二十一
What is happiness?
This is an age-old question that has been puzzling people from all walks of life.
Although different people has different opinions about it,
we all agree that it is such a precious thing
that cannot be bought by money or anything else.
And despite many scientific studies carried out on happiness,
no really effective way to gain happiness has yet been found and introduced.
Everyone wants to live a happy life and to find happiness at every turn.
But what should we do then?
My answer is we should do something rather than wait passively.
Sages told us hundreds of years ago that when we give,
we are far happier than when we receive.
That means we are responsible for other people's happiness
and we should take the initiative in securing happiness.
We always have to be ready to give a hand to people in need.
We should form a supportive network with people around us.
Only in this way are we able to find true life-time happiness.
Happiness is all around us in our daily life.
All we have to do is make an effort to be happy and to make others happy.
So don't hesitate to focus on other people's happiness,
in other words, value the pursuit of happiness for ourselves and for others.
Remember: “Life is what you make it. So make it happy.”